Build a contract from source

Builds all crates that are referenced by the cargo manifest (Cargo.toml) that have cdylib as their crate-type. Crates are built for the wasm32 target. Unless configured otherwise, crates are built with their default features and with their release profile.

In workspaces builds all crates unless a package name is specified, or the command is executed from the sub-directory of a workspace crate.

To view the commands that will be executed, without executing them, use the --print-commands-only option.

Usage: stellar.exe contract build [OPTIONS]

Options:
      --manifest-path <MANIFEST_PATH>
          Path to Cargo.toml

      --package <PACKAGE>
          Package to build
          
          If omitted, all packages that build for crate-type cdylib are built.

      --profile <PROFILE>
          Build with the specified profile
          
          [default: release]

      --out-dir <OUT_DIR>
          Directory to copy wasm files to
          
          If provided, wasm files can be found in the cargo target directory, and the specified directory.
          
          If ommitted, wasm files are written only to the cargo target directory.

      --optimize
          Optimize the generated wasm

  -h, --help
          Print help (see a summary with '-h')

Features:
      --features <FEATURES>
          Build with the list of features activated, space or comma separated

      --all-features
          Build with the all features activated

      --no-default-features
          Build with the default feature not activated

Other:
      --print-commands-only
          Print commands to build without executing them

Metadata:
      --meta <META>
          Add key-value to contract meta (adds the meta to the `contractmetav0` custom section)

Options (Global):
      --global
          ΓÜá∩╕Å Deprecated: global config is always on

      --config-dir <CONFIG_DIR>
          Location of config directory. By default, it uses `$XDG_CONFIG_HOME/stellar` if set, falling back to `~/.config/stellar` otherwise. Contains configuration files, aliases, and other persistent settings

  -f, --filter-logs <FILTER_LOGS>
          Filter logs output. To turn on `stellar_cli::log::footprint=debug` or off `=off`. Can also use env var `RUST_LOG`

  -q, --quiet
          Do not write logs to stderr including `INFO`

  -v, --verbose
          Log DEBUG events

      --very-verbose
          Log DEBUG and TRACE events
          
          [aliases: --vv]

      --no-cache
          Do not cache your simulations and transactions
          
          [env: STELLAR_NO_CACHE=]
